saar-bank.com 2015-03-16

# Saar Bank

We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, etc) subject to the Terms and Conditions and of this Privacy Policy. We will not sell, barter, rent or share your personal information to third parties, except as described in this privacy statement.

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of our clients and those who visit our Website. We protect our members information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the highest standards. In addition, we will limit the collection and use of nonpublic personal information to the minimum required. We restrict access to your personal account information only to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you.

We use encryption, firewall, router, third party verification procedures and other sophisticated security software and hardware to help prevent unauthorized access to members confidential and private information.

To provide better service and a more effective Website, we use "cookies" as part of our interaction with your browser. A "cookie" is a small, text file placed on your hard drive by our webpage server. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to determine who you are or your e-mail address. We use cookies to determine if you have previously visited our Website and for several administration purposes.

We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. In such a case, all OlympicCoin members will be notified by e-mail and given the option to opt-out of future communication if desired.

We may disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law (for example about any person who is trying fraudulent actions), and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice before disclosure in such cases.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by OlympicCoin may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, and other service related communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our Website (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will share personally identifiable information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

We follow the same privacy policies and practices for former members as are described in this notice.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our homepage and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it.
